browsergamez.com 2018-04-23

# Privacy note

## Information about data collection, processing, and use

For adspree media GmbH, Schlesische Str. 27, 10997 Berlin (in the following abbreviated “ASM”), your trust in the correct handling of your data is an important precondition for the success of the service offered by ASM. Your data is collected, processed (includes storing, changing, transferring, blocking, and deleting), and used exclusively in accordance with applicable data protection provisions.

#### 1\. Collection, processing, and use of personal data

 **a) What is personal data?**

Personal data is information about the identity of an individual such as e.g. name, address, telephone and fax number, date of birth, or e-mail address.

 **b) Is personal data collected, processed, and used when the online service is used?**

The service can generally be used without personal data being stored. To the extent that personal data is nevertheless collected, processed, and used, ASM informs you where appropriate or asks you to provide your personal data – for example to participate in a contest or to register for a specific service. In any such case, your personal data is collected, processed, and used only for that specific purpose and in accordance with the principle of data minimization.

Below you can find several examples where we collect, process, and use personal data:

• Contests

If you decide to take part in a contest that we have organized, we will ask you to provide us your name and date of birth, your e-mail address, your telephone number, and/or your postal address, particularly so that we can inform you in case you win, but also to ensure that each participant only participates in the contest once.

• Subscribing to offers/information (e.g. by newsletter)

As part of our online service, we offer you the opportunity to receive information about interesting offers and news from us in various ways (e-mail, telephone, and/or SMS/MMS). If, for example, you have added your name to the distribution list of one of our newsletters, you will regularly receive the requested newsletter at your e-mail address. When registering for a newsletter, you may also have the opportunity to provide further details about yourself, if you would like to receive a birthday surprise, for example. We will then process and use the data provided by you for these purposes.

All personal data provided by you will only be collected, processed, and used by ASM as the responsible entity. ASM will not transfer your personal data to third parties, particularly not to other enterprises or other organizations, unless you explicitly consent to this or ASM is required by law to transfer this data, e.g. based on a court order or at the instruction of public authorities. If ASM contracts with third parties for a commissioned data processing pursuant to Section 11 of the German Federal Data Protection Act (BDASM) for the collection, processing, and use of data, this also is conducted exclusively in accordance with the statutory data protection provisions.

#### 2\. Collection, processing, and use of usage data

 **a) What is usage data?**

Usage data is data that may be collected each time you are browsing any website.

 **b) How is usage data collected, processed, and used when this service is used?**

When you are accessing the services, ASM briefly stores your usage data for a period of four (4) working days. The usage data being stored is: the domain name or IP address of the inquiring computer, the client’s file inquiry (file name and URL), the http response code, the Internet site from which you are visiting us, as well as the date and duration of your visit. This data is stored to determine disruptions or abuse of our online service and of our telecommunication services/systems insofar as this is necessary to establish the telecommunication connection and/or to invoice the service. Your usage data is not analyzed to create a personal user profile unless you have specifically consented to such use. In the case of disruptions or abuse, we reserve the right to report this to a law enforcement agency. There is no further use or disclosure of your usage data collected in this manner to third parties.

If data is required to fulfill existing legal, statutory, or contractual storage periods (including such storage periods which result from contractual relationships with third parties), we will block the data in accordance with applicable legal provisions. All usage data will only be collected, processed, and used by ASM as the responsible entity. ASM will not transfer your personal data to third parties, particularly not to other enterprises or other organizations, unless you explicitly consent to this or ASM is required by law to transfer this data, e.g. based on a court order or at the instruction of public authorities. If ASM contracts with third parties for a commissioned data processing pursuant to Section 11 of the German Federal Data Protection Act BDASM for the collection, processing, and use of data, this is conducted exclusively in accordance with the statutory data protection provisions.

#### 3\. Data correction and withdrawal of consent

If you are no longer interested in receiving certain information or offers and/or no longer wish to receive the information/offers via a certain media, please send an e-mail to the following address: [datenschutz@p7s1games.net](mailto:datenschutz@p7s1games.net). ASM will meet your request promptly. In this case, all your data stored in this context will be deleted without undue delay, if this is possible considering the purpose of the contract and unless a deletion is prevented by mandatory legal reasons. Please note that due to technical or organizational reasons, the use of your data during an ongoing campaign may overlap with the withdrawal of your consent.

#### 4\. Use of cookies

We would like to point out that this service uses cookies. The visitor’s/user’s acceptance of these cookies is not a precondition for the use of the service. However, not all functions may be accessible when cookies are blocked.

 **a) What are cookies?**

A cookie is a small text file sent by the respective web servers when the service is visited and is stored on the hard drive of the respective user. If the relevant server is accessed again, the user’s browser sends the previously received cookie back to the server. The server can then analyze the information received through this procedure in various ways. There are generally two kinds of cookies. On the one side, there are session cookies, which are stored only for the respective user session. This means that the cookies are deleted automatically when the respective service is closed by the user/visitor. On the other side, there are temporary/permanent cookies, which are stored for a longer period or indefinitely on the user’s data media.

 **b) How does ASM use cookies?**

ASM uses both session cookies and temporary/permanent cookies in its services. When a user visits a service, cookies are sent to the user’s browser and stored on the user’s hard drive. These cookies make our online service more user-friendly, more effective, and more secure. The cookies do not contain any personal data and/or personal information about the user so that it is not possible for us to identify the individual using the information received via cookies. The generated information is used exclusively for the purpose of generating statistics on the use of our online service. We can thereby adapt our online service to your requirements in the best possible manner. The session cookies are deleted automatically from the customer’s hard drive after the end of the browser session. ASM also uses cookies that remain permanently on the user’s hard drive. These cookies are necessary to recognize a user the next time the site is visited and to determine which settings and inputs this visitor requires. These cookies remain on the hard drive and auto-delete after the predetermined time has expired.

 **c) Which data is contained in the cookies?**

The cookies are used to store information about certain usage behavior, visited pages of the ASM services, etc. However, no personal data is stored. The stored cookies therefore do not make it possible to attribute usage behavior to a specified or determinable individual. To the extent that cookies are used, encrypted numbers are attributed to them. However, these cookies do not contain the name, IP address, addresses, and other personal data, and it is not possible to attribute any personal data to the cookie ident numbers at any time. The information transferred to ASM is so general that we merely receive information about which pages were visited or which individual pages were clicked on the website. This information is only transferred and stored under a pseudonym, which cannot be attributed to the name. The storage accordingly only serves our own review of the efficiency of ASM’s website content and not to analyze personal usage behavior of determinable individual users.

 **d) Are third-party provider cookies or web beacons and user-based online advertising also used?**

Advertising in this online service is optimized for you by forecasting your interests by anonymously collecting and processing your user behavior. For this purpose, we use third-party providers to place cookies on your computer that collect usage data. This is data that may be collected while you are e.g. using the websites of this online service or click on advertising. We are thereby able to analyze the use of online advertising, which may be of interest for you and meet your preferences („ **usage-based online advertising** “). We never store any personal data (such as name, address, e-mail address) in this context. Any IP addresses that may be collected are anonymized so that it becomes impossible to attribute these to an individual.

If you no longer want to receive any usage-based online advertising, you can prevent cookies from being set or stored in your browser settings. You can also object to the use of cookies by the third-party companies working for us via the links below:

 **Nugg.ad AG:** <http://ad-choices.nuggad.net/>

**AdAudience GmbH/AudienceScience:** <http://www.adaudience.de/index.php?id=23>

**AudienceScience:** <http://www.audiencescience.com/privacy/>

**Criteo GmbH:** <http://www.criteo.com/en/privacy-policy/>

Our online service uses Google AdSense, a web service offered by Google Inc., USA („ **Google** “), which places third-party advertisements („ **adverts** “) on our online service. We would therefore like to make you aware that through these adverts, Google may place and read cookies on your browsers and may use so-called “web beacons” (small invisible graphic files) to collect information. The information generated by these cookies and/or web beacons is transferred to a Google server in the USA and processed there.

The use of the so-called DoubleClick DART cookie enables Google to use information about your visits to our online service and other websites so that certain adverts are controlled by so-called frequency capping. The frequency of adverts is thereby ensured using standardized criteria. You can deactivate the use of the Double Click DART cookie on the Google website by clicking on the “Advertising” policy in Google’s “Policies & Principles” and following the instruction there regarding deactivation.

Further information regarding usage-based online advertising is also available on the consumer portal meine-cookies.org under [www.meine-cookies.org](http://www.meine-cookies.org/). Under meine-cookies.org, you can furthermore also deactivate or activate the collection of usage data by and check the activation status at various service providers using the following link: [www.meine-cookies.org/cookies_verwalten/praeferenzmanager-beta.html](http://www.meine-cookies.org/cookies_verwalten/praeferenzmanager-beta.html).

We also allow other third parties to set cookies to create anonymous usage statistics and use the data for market research purposes. Attributing that data to an individual is not possible.

You can also prevent third-party cookies from being placed by configuring your browser accordingly.

We use the following tracking tools in our service:

 **IVW/AGOF**

This online service uses the “Scalable Central Measurement Method” (Skalierbare Zentrale Messverfahren - SZM) of the company INFOnline ([https://www.infonline.de](https://www.infonline.de/)) to determine statistical parameters for the use of the online service. Anonymous measurements are collected here. In order to recognize computer systems, the SZM online audience measurement uses either a cookie with the identifier “ivwbox.de” or a signature created from various information of your computer that is transferred automatically. This method does not store IP addresses and processes them only in an anonymised form. The ratings measurement was developed in compliance with data protection. Purpose of the ratings measurement is to statistically determine the usage intensity and number of users of a website. Individual users are not identified at any time. Your identity always remains protected. You do not receive any advertisement through the system. For web services that are members of the German Information Association for Determining the Distribution of Advertising Media registered association (Informationsgemeinschaft zur Feststellung der Verbreitung von Werbeträgern e.V. (IVW) – [www.ivw.eu](http://www.ivw.eu/)) or who participate in the study “Internet Facts” of the Workgroup Online Research registered association (Arbeitsgemeinschaft Online-Forschung e.V. (AGOF) – [www.agof.de](http://www.agof.de/)), the usage statistics are published monthly by the AGOF and the Workgroup Media Analysis registered association (Arbeitsgemeinschaft Media-Analyse e.V. (ag.ma) - [www.agma-mmc.de](http://www.agma-mmc.de/)) and by the IVW and can be accessed under [http://www.agof.de](http://www.agof.de/), [http://www.agma-mmc.de](http://www.agma-mmc.de/) and [http://www.ivw.eu](http://www.ivw.eu/). In addition to publishing measurements data, the IVW regularly reviews the SZM procedure for rule- and data protection-compliant use. You can find further information about the SZM procedure on the website of INFOnline GmbH ([https://www.infonline.de](https://www.infonline.de/)) who operates the SZM procedure, the data protection website of AGOF (<http://www.agof.de/datenschutz>), and on the data protection website of IVW ([www.ivw.eu](http://www.ivw.eu/)). You can opt out from the data processing by the SZM under the following link: [http://optout.ivwbox.de](http://optout.ivwbox.de/).

 **Google Analytics**

This offer uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google Inc., USA ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies that make it possible to analyze your use of our online service. The information generated by the cookies about your use of our service (including your IP address) are transferred to a server of Google in Europe or in a member state of the European Economic Area for anonymization of the IP address, so that it is no longer possible to establish a link to a person. Only after anonymization of the IP address is this abbreviated IP address transferred to a server located in the USA. The full IP address is transferred to a Google server in the USA and abbreviated there only in exceptional cases. We have asked Google to use the information generated by the cookies to analyze your use of the service, to compile reports about the use of the service, and in order to provide additional services related to the use of the service and general Internet use. The (abbreviated) IP address is not combined with other Google data. In addition to the Browser settings mentioned above, you can prevent your data from being processed by Google by downloading and installing the browser plugin that is available under the following link: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de.

 **e) What is Onsite-Targeting?**

ASM’s website uses the cookies referred to above (session cookies and temporary cookies) to optimize advertising offers. However, no attribution to the respective individual can be done here either. This involves only data that is collected to optimize the website. The data is used to provide advertising/special offers and services that are tailored to the respective user. This makes the service even more attractive for the customer and can be used better and more customer-friendly. This is the only way to offer advertising/services tailored to the respective customer interests. The customer accordingly only receives advertising that really interests him or her and not a wide range of general advertising. Nevertheless, the customer may certainly revoke his consent to having advertising sent to him generally at all times.

 **f) What is Re-Targeting?**

Re-Targeting works similar to Onsite-Targeting. The main difference is that third-party companies are involved in the Re-Targeting. ASM’s service also uses so-called Re-Targeting software. This technology makes it possible for a user to be addressed with advertising also on websites of partners of ASM. The user can thereby be provided with interest-based advertising, which goes even beyond the range of services offered by ASM. The cookies referred to above (session cookies and temporary cookies) are also used for this purpose, with which the previous usage behavior is analyzed. No personal data is stored and no personal data is passed on in this case either. ASM’s partner receives no personal data of the user either. Advertising is merely also shown on the partner’s web pages without the data (cookies storing usage behavior) being combined with the personal data of a determinable individual. It is not possible for the third party to combine the usage behavior with the respective individual.

 **g) How is it generally possible to prevent that cookies are set?**

A user may also permanently or even temporarily prevent cookies from being placed in general through corresponding browser settings (please click here for detailed information). If the customer sets up the browser accordingly, it is possible that he or she can no longer use all of the services and/or functions offered by us. Each browser can be set so that cookies are generally rejected. If a customer wants to keep cookies from being set, he or she should please follow these technical instructions.

#### 5\. Use of so-called Social Plugins

On the website of these services, the Social Plugins of the social network www.facebook.com, which is operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S.California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA ("Facebook") are integrated. The Facebook recommendation function, the Facebook “Like Button”, the Facebook “Share Button”, the Facebook “Live Stream”, and the Facebook comment box are examples for such a so-called Social Plugin. These functions are subject to constant development and expansion by Facebook. Such a so-called Social Plugin is marked using a clearly visible Facebook logo (e.g. white “f” on a blue tile or a “Thumbs Up” sign) or the addition "Facebook Social Plugin". If a corresponding website is accessed, which contains such so-called Social Plugins, the user’s browser directly connects to the Facebook servers. If the user is registered with Facebook and logged into his or her Facebook account, Facebook receives the information that the corresponding website was accessed by the user. If the user then uses a so-called Social Plugin actively, e.g. by using the “Like” button or the “Share” button or by posting a comment in the comment box on the relevant website, the corresponding information is transferred by the user’s browser directly to Facebook and used there. In order to avoid that Facebook collects the aforementioned information when a corresponding website is accessed, the user is advised to obtain information about this on the Facebook website and/or to log off Facebook before accessing a website with a so-called Social Plugin. In addition, the user should delete any existing Facebook cookies from his or her browser.

The purpose and scope of the data collection and the further use of the data by Facebook as well as the related rights and set-up options for the protection of privacy should be obtained from the Facebook data protection information. Please note insofar that Facebook continuously enhances the social network and provides information about the related data use. The web pages of this online service use Social Plugins of Google +1 of the social network Google Plus, which is operated by Google. The button can be recognized by the sign "+1" on white or colored background. If you access a web page of our online service that contains such a button, your computer’s browser directly connects to the Google servers. The content of the "+1" button is transferred directly from Google to your browser and embedded into the web page by it. We therefore have no influence over the scope of data that Google collects with the button. According to Google, no personal data is collected without a click on the button. Such data, including the IP address, is collected and processed only for members that are logged-in. If you are a Google Plus member and do not want Google to collect data about you via our online service and link them to your membership data stored with Google, you have to log off Google Plus before visiting our Internet presence. The purpose and scope of the data collection and the further use of the data by Google as well as your related rights and set-up options for the protection of your privacy can be found in Google’s data protection policies for the "+1" button: <http://www.google.com/intl/de/+/policy/+1button.html> and the FAQ of bit.ly

#### 6\. No liability for partner websites and data protection terms

ASM’s web pages contain links to various cooperation partners, who offer tele media services, particularly websites, themselves. They usually provide their own data protection policies. ASM does not assume any liability for these policies that are not connected with ASM. Please consult the respective data protection policy directly at those sites.

#### 7\. Data security

ASM takes all reasonable technical and organizational measures in order to ensure the safe collection, processing, and use of your data. In order to prevent unauthorized access or unauthorized disclosure and to ensure the correctness of the data and authorized use of the data, ASM has established corresponding technical and organizational procedures in order to secure and protect the data that ASM collects online. However, ASM cannot accept responsibility or liability for the disclosure of your data due to errors during data transmission and/or unauthorized third-party access. ASM endeavors to handle your personal data responsibly, particularly to protect and preserve your privacy.

#### 8\. Information / suggestions

For further information and suggestions on the issue of data protection, you can reach ASM under the e-mail address [datenschutz@p7s1games.net](mailto:datenschutz@p7s1games.net).

#### 9\. Amendment of data protection terms

ASM reserves the right to amend these Data Protection Terms at any time in accordance with applicable data protection laws. If you have issued your consent during registration in respect to these Data Protection Terms, ASM undertakes to inform you about any amendment of these Data Protection Terms in an appropriate manner.

 **Date: 20 February 2014**

## Technical Information

#### To reject cookies:

 **Internet Explorer:**

Tools Menu – Internet Options  
“Privacy” tab: click on the “Sites…“ button

Enter the text “http://sevengames.com” in the “Address of website:” field and confirm it by clicking the “Block” button. The browser will then no longer use any cookies for “http://sevengames.com” while other websites remain unaffected.

 **Mozilla Firefox:**

Tools – Options  
“Privacy” section: Cookies  
Click on the “Exceptions” button

Enter the text “http://sevengames.com” in the field “Website Address:” and confirm it by clicking the button “Block”. The browser will then no longer use any cookies for “http://sevengames.com” while other websites remain unaffected.

 **Chrome:**

Open the Chrome menu (symbol in the top right corner of your browser)   
Select “Options” there   
At the bottom of the text, click on “Show further options…”  
In the Data Protection section open “Content Settings…”

In the Cookies section open “Manage exceptions…” and enter the text “http://sevengames.com” (without quotation marks). By clicking on “Block” you prevent cookies of this website from being used while other websites remain unaffected.
